Sorry about earlier.
ごめん、さっきは
Are you angry?
怒ってる?
I'm angry.
怒ってるわ
i don't know.
知らない
When I told him that my dad put it out.
パパが出したって言ったら
Well, that's true.
まあ、そうなんだけど
Well, um, no, this about me.
まあ、あの、いや、 私の事のこの、
Well, I guess you could say I forced myself to do it, but I guess I just got used to it.
ね、無理やりだしたって言うか、 なれちゃったみたいな
I'm used to it.
なれちゃったじゃない
thank you.
ありがとう
Sorry.
ごめんね
No, I'm not sorry, but what if I get pregnant?
いや、ごめんねじゃないし、妊娠したらどうするの?
Well, yes.
まあ、そう
Well, it's not like I'm thinking that much about myself.
まあ、でも、 俺の事、そこまで考えてるわけじゃないんで、
You'll be fine if you do that.
そうやっても大丈夫になります
I don't know if it's okay
大丈夫かどうか分か
No.
ん ない
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry.
ごめん、本当にごめんね
sorry.
ごめん
Please forgive me, I'm sorry.
許してください、ごめん
Are you really remorseful?
本当に反省してる?
All I can do is reflect.
反省しかしてない
A world of reflection.
反省の世界
I am now in a world of reflection.
反省の世界に入ってる、今
I'll be really angry next time.
次したら本当に怒るよ
There's more left across the street.
向かい余って
Go take a shower.
シャワーするから行って
Don't say that.
なんて言わないで
picture?
え?
Well then, take a shower.
じゃあ、シャワー
Did you make up?
仲直しした?
good.
よかった
We made up.
仲直した
It's beautiful.
綺麗じゃん
I'll be waiting.
待ってるからね